BRAC Additional Records 5735
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- International Affairs - Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores (Interamerican Regional Organization of Workers), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  January-July 16, 1974
- International Affairs - American Trade Union Council for Histadrut, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  1976-January 11, 1978
- Foreign Organizations - General, 1960-1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  1960-March 26, 1973
- Foreign Organizations - India, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  January-February 12, 1974
- Foreign Organizations - Israel, National Committee Trade Union Council (Histadrut), 1965-1979 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  January 1, 1965-May 31, 1979
- African American Organizations, 1959-1978 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  1959-April 7, 1978.
- African American Organizations - A. Philip Randolph Institute, National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  May-December 13, 1979
- African American Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1959-1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  1959-July 13, 1978
- Special File - LABOR Newspaper - C.L. Dennis, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- LABOR Newspaper, 1970-1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  January 1, 1970-October 1979
- LABOR Newspaper - Financial Statements, 1970-1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  January 1, 1970-November 1976
- LABOR Newspaper - Annual Meetings, Special Meetings, 1974-1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  January 1974-March 19, 1979
- LABOR Newspaper - Certificate of Membership, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- LABOR Newspaper - History of LABOR, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- District Councils, 1961-1978 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  January 1, 1961-October 1978
- District Councils - Chicago, 1970-1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  January 1, 1970-December 1979
- District Councils - Greater Detroit, 1971-1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  November 1971-September 1976. See File 206-8 for By-Laws.
- District Councils - East Saint Louis, 1947-1979 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  1947-March 1979. See 206-21 for By-Laws
- District Councils - Minneapolis-Saint Paul, 1960-1979 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  1960-December 1979
- District Councils - Greater New York, 1961-1979 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  1961-August 1979
- Special Dispensations, 1959-1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  1959-July 12, 1971
- Railway Business Women's Association, 1960-1971 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  1960-April 24, 1971
- Internal Revenue, 1960-1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  1960-January 13, 1976
- Death Benefit Department - Claims, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  January 1, 1971-August 19, 1974
- Death Benefit Department, 1974-1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  January 1974-August 23, 1979
- Meeting of Labor Organization With Air Transport Membership, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Preliminary Task Force on Productivity in the Railroad Industry, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Transportation, 1973-1977 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  June 1973-April 1977
- Transportation, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  March 1975-April 1977
- Transportation, 1977-1983 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  May 1977-March 1983
- Employment - Grand Lodge, 1973-1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  July 1, 1973-December 12, 1979
- Grand Lodge - Employment, Illinois State Employment Service, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  May 1975-July 26, 1977
- Conference on Economic Progress, 1964-1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  October 1, 1964-February 4, 1976. Includes Bound Material
- Disaster Relief - Financial Assistance, 1967-1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  January 1, 1967-October 1979
- Disaster Relief - Contributions, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Disaster Relief - Financial Assistance, Contributions, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Grand Lodge - Miscellaneous, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Conferences, 1960-1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  1960-October 1978
- Educational Conferences, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  May 18-19, 1972
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  November 22, 1974-August 1975
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  September 1975-July 1976
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  August 1976-May 1979
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  January-June 1979
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Community Service Activities, 1966-1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  January 1, 1966-March 1973
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Executive Committee, 1956-1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  1956- November 1972. Includes Bound Materials.
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Labor Studies Center, 1970-1974 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  July 1970- January 1974
- Latin America, 1971-1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Council for Professional Employees (Formerly Council of AFL-CIO Unions for Scientific, Professional, and Cultural Employees [S.P.A.C.E.]), 1969-1979 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  May 1, 1969-December 1979
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Conventions, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  November 1971
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Committee on Education, 1962-1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  May 19, 1962-March 6, 1975
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Labor Management, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Conference of Transportation Trades, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  January 1, 1970
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Conference of Transportation Trades, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Human Resources Development Institute, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Maritime Trades Department, 1973-1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  September 1973-July 9, 1979. Includes bound materials.
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Maritime Trades Department, 1969-1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  June 1, 1969-August 1973
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Central Labor Councils, 1973-1979 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  1973- September 1979
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - C.L. Dennis Elected to Executive Council, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Per Capita Tax, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  March 1982
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Executive Council, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  August 1973- December 1974. Includes bumper stickers, stickers, and other miscellany. Large folder which is getting a bit worn down. If pulled, you may want to replace it.
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Executive Council, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  January-October 1975
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Executive Council, 1975-1977 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  November 1975-April 1977
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations - Executive Council Statements, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  August 1970
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Booklets, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  Includes Bound Materials.
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Political Programs, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  January 1974
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Labor Life Insurance Company, 1952-1971 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  Includes bound materials
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Labor Life Insurance Company, 1957-1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  January 1, 1957-April 1973
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Brotherhood Charter, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Label and Service Trades Department, 1971-1979 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  June 23, 1971-June 1979
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Label and Services Trades Department Booth, Union Industries Show, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  Includes Pamphlets and Floor Plans. Atlanta, Georgia. May 14-19, 1971.
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Label and Service Trades Department, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  Includes Pamphlets. 1973 Twin Cities Union-Industries Show. Minneapolis, Minnesota.
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Label and Service Trades Department, New York State - Labor-Management Exhibit, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  June 18-20, 1971. Rochester, New York.
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Label and Service Trades Department, San Diego Union Industry Show, 1963- 1972 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  January 1, 1963-July 1972. San Diego Union Industry Show 1972. Includes Bound Materials.
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - "Union-Industries Show", 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  Material from August 1973 for Union Industries Show, Memphis, Tennessee 1974.
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Union Industries Show, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Milwaukee, Wisconsin. 1974-May 1975
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - International Labor Committee (International Affairs), 1973 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  June 1973
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Internal Disputes Plan: Determinations Made by Impartial Umpire Under the Terms of Article XXI of the AFL-CIO Constitution, 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Internal Disputes Plan, 1975-1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  May 1975- May 1979
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Internal Disputes Plan, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  June 1979-December 1979
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations - Internal Disputes Plan, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Internal Disputes Plan: Determinations and Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  Bound.
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Building and Construction Trades Department, United Steelworkers of America, 1963- 1964 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1973-1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  July 1973-July 1979
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Research Department, 1963-1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  January 1, 1963-April 1976
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Labor Legislation, Special Executive Council Sub Committee, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Ethical Practices, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  1972-June 1973
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Advisory Committee on Foreign Trade Policy, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  May 1975
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Latin American Advancement (LCLAA), 1976-1979 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  1976-June 1979
- Canadian Labour Congress, 1968-1979 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  January 1, 1968-July 1979. Includes bound materials.
- Canadian Labour Congress - Union-Industries Show, Kitchener, Ontario, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  September 21, 1970-December 1970
- Canadian Labour Congress - Union Industries Show, London, Ontario, Canada, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  October 2-6, 1971
- Canadian Labour Congress - Per Capita Tax, 1960-1972 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  1960-June 1972
- Canadian Labour Congress - Tenth Constitutional Convention, Pacific National Exhibition Grounds, Vancouver, British Columbia, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  May 13-17, 1974. CL Dennis
- Canadian Labour Congress - Conventions, 1964-1979 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  January 1, 1964-December 1979
- Interstate Commerce Commission, 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  January 1, 1970-May 1973
- Interstate Commerce Commission, 1973-1977 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  June 1973-May 1977
- Interstate Commerce Commission, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  June 1977-December 1979
- Memorandum on the Problem of Having Employees of Transportation Companies Which Are Subsidiaries of Rail Carriers Considered as Rail Employees (Box 19, Folder 16)
  No date
- Interstate Commerce Commission - 10% Increase in Freight and Charges, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  June 1974
- Interstate Commerce Commission - Rail Services Planning Office, Rail Merger Study (Initial Paper), 1977 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  April 15, 1977. Bound.
- Interstate Commerce Commission - Rail Services Planning Office, Rail Merger Study (Initial Paper), 1977 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Bound. April 15, 1977.
- Interstate Commerce Commission - Ex Parte 72 Sub 1, 1959-1966 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  1959-September 28, 1966
- Interstate Commerce Commission - Interstate Commerce Commission Ex Parte Number 72 Sub 1, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  1969- December 31, 1970
- Interstate Commerce Commission - Decisions Rendered Under Ex Parte 72 Sub 1 (Including Index), 1965 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  August 12, 1965
- Interstate Commerce Commission - ICC Ex Parte Number 274 Sub 1-8, Abandonment of Railroad Lines, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  January 2, 1979
- Interstate Commerce Commission - ICC Ex Parte Number 305, Increased Freight Rates and Charges, 1975: Recyclable Materials, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Interstate Commerce Commission - Determination of Status of Auxiliary and Supplemental Rail Service by Motor Carriers, 1966-1971 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  1966-January 1971
- Interstate Commerce Commission - Rail Merger Studies, Rail Services Planning Office, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  Includes Bound Materials
- Interstate Commerce Commission - Proposed Changes in Interstate Commerce Commission Forms A and B and N-300, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  1968-May 1971
- Interstate Commerce Commission - M-300 Reports, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  March 1979-?
- Interstate Commerce Commission - Rail Services Planning Office, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations on GA-23000, GA-23111, GA-107300, GA-107300L, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  September 1971 Meeting
- Health and Welfare (General), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  July 1979-December 12, 1979
- Rules - Health and Welfare Policy GA 23000, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  December 20, 1976-September 1977
- Rules - Health and Welfare Policy GA-23000, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  October 1977-July 1979
- Rules - Health and Welfare Policy GA-23000, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  August-October 1979
- Group Policy GA-46000, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  February 1979-December 19, 1979
- United States Congressional Railway Studies, 1975-1979 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Employees' Grand President's Office - Instructions, 1973-1978 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  January 1973-August 1978
- Supplies (General), 1978 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  October 6, 1978
- Employees Grand President's Office (General), 1973-1979 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  December 1, 1973-November 29, 1979
- Grand Lodge Office Employees ("Miscellaneous Junk"), 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  October 17, 1969-June 30, 1970
- International President's Office - Vacations, 1972-1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  1972-June 4, 1979
- Leave of Absence, 1972-1978 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  1972-October 5, 1978
- Employees International President's Office - Assignment of Duties, 1965-1979 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  January 1, 1965-December 21, 1979
- Acts of Congress - Railway Labor Act, 1971-1979 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  June 1971-July 3, 1979
- Employees International President's Office - Instructions, 1970-1979 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  June 16, 1970-December 13, 1979
- Overtime - Contract Employees, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  November 1979
- Employees International President's Office - Working Conditions, 1972-1975 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  1972-October 30, 1975
- Employees International President's Office - Rates of Pay, 1976-1979 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  1976-June 5, 1979
- United States Congress (General), 1979 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- United States Congress (General), 1979 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  July-October 1979
- United States Congress (General), 1979 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  November-December 1979
- Natural Gas Act - Deregulation of Natural Gas, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Legislative Capsule, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  June 1976
- Federal Workmen's Compensation, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  May-December 1979
- United States Congress - Highways, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- United States Congress - Railroad Reorganization Act, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  Replacement of Original File. June 1975.
- United States Congress - Hours of Service, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  Replacement of Original File. March 1976.
- Legislative - National Industrial Recovery Act, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- United States Congress - Interstate Commerce Act, 1961-1975 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  June 1, 1961-June 1975
- United States Congress - Federal Employers' Liability Act, 1957-1978 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  Note: see Separate File for Legal Aid Department. January 1, 1957-October 1978
- Federal Employers' Liability Act - Legal Assistance Department, 1973-1979 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  July 1, 1973-December 1979
- United States Congress - Rivers and Harbors, 1974-1977 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  November 1974-August 1977
- United State Congress - Rivers and Harbors, 1977-1979 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  September 1977-March 1979
- United States Congress - Railroad Retirement - March on Washington - HR 7200, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  1973-July 1974
- United States Congress - Railroad Retirement Act (President's Commission on Railroad Retirement), 1972-1979 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  May 1, 1972- May 15, 1979
- United States Congress - Railroad Retirement Board Educational and Informational Conferences, 1974-1979 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  January 1, 1974- February 22, 1979
- Railroad Retirement Act (General), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  May 1, 1979-December 22, 1979
- Acts of Congress - Railroad Retirement Act - Medicare, 1973-1978 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  1973-November 1978
- Railroad Retirement Special File for Monthly Benefit Statistics Report, 1973-1979 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  May 1973-January 1979
- Railroad Retirement Act - A Bill to Amend the Railroad Retirement Act of 1937, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  June 30, 1974
- Railroad Retirement Act - Proposed Amendments, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  March 1970
- United States Congress - Proposed Amendments, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Railroad Retirement Act - Proposed Amendments, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Railroad Retirement Act - Proposed Amendments, 1974-1979 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  December 1974-June 1979
- Railroad Retirement Act - Itinerant Service, 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  January 1, 1974-1977
- Railroad Retirement Board - Itinerant Service (Fred Williams), 1974-1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  January 1974-February 23, 1976
- Railroad Retirement Board - Itinerant Service (General), 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  January 1978-June 15, 1979
- Railroad Retirement Act - Copies of Material Distributed to Chief Executives, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Railroad Retirement Act - Joint Labor-Management Railroad Retirement Committee (C.L. Dennis), 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  July 24, 1973- January 8, 1974
- Railroad Retirement Act - Booklets, 1961-1971 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  Includes Bound Material. February 1, 1961-March 1971
- Railroad Retirement Act - Railway Labor Executives Association, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  May-June 1979
- Railroad Retirement (Miscellaneous), 1974 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Railroad Retirement - Subsidiaries or Spinoffs of Railroads, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  1976-April 1977
- Railroad Retirement Act - Supplemental Pensions (C.L. Dennis - Work File), 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Railroad Retirement Act - Supplemental Annuities, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  January 1, 1974
- Railroad Retirement Act - Questions and Answers, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  August 1, 1971
- Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act, 1963-1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  Misinterpretation of the provisions of Section 308 of the Public Law 86-28, which authorized the borrowing of monies in the Railroad Retirement account of the United States Treasury. Vicious propaganda circulated by the self-styled "Railroad Pension Commi
- Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act (General), 1973-1978 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  January 1973-December 1978
- Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act (General), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  January-November 1979
- Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act - Proposed Amendments, 1960-1971 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  January 1, 1960-August 1971
- Railroad Unemployment and Sickness Insurance Act - Claims, 1972-1976 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  January 1, 1972-October 31, 1976
- Railroad Unemployment and Sickness Insurance Act - Claims, 1976-1979 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  November 1976-January 1979
- Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act - Weekly Report of the Board - Benefits Paid for Unemployment, Sickness, and Maternity, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  January 1, 1974-April 1976
- Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act - Weekly Report of the Board - Weekly Reports, 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  May 1976-October 1978
- International Labor Organizations, 1972-1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  January 18, 1972-April 1976
- United States Congress - Pensions, Old Age, 1972-1976 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  March 23, 1972-March 1976
- Special File C.L. Dennis - Report on Railroad Retirement and Medicare, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  March 15, 1974
- United States Congress - National Labor Relations Act, 1963-1979 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- United States Congress - Labor Contracts (H.R. Bills), 1969 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  Old File Not Returned
- The President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped - Membership Directory, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  Bound. September 1977
- United States Congress - Employment of Physically Handicapped, 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  January 1, 1966-June 1969. Includes Bound Materials.
- United States Congress - Employment of the Handicapped, 1973-1979 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  November 1973-July 1979
- United States Congress - Social Security Act, Medicare H.R. 6675, 1965-1970 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  June 1, 1965-March 1970. Includes Bound Materials.
- United States Congress - Social Security Act, 1967-1978 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  August 4, 1967-November 1978
- United States Congress - Registration of Lobbyists, 1973-1979 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  1973-January 1979
- United States Congress - Civil Aeronautics Board - Mutual Aid Pact, 1964-1979 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  January 1, 1964-October 1979
- United States Congress - Civil Aeronautics Board - Renewal of Mutual Aid Pact, 1970-1972 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  1970-March 1972
- Civil Aeronautics Board, 1963-1977 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  May 7, 1963-August 1977
- Civil Aeronautics Board - Mutual Aid Pact Docket 9977, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- United States Congress - Civil Aeronautics Board - Renewal of Mutual Aid Pact, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  Found Empty December 8, 2014
- Fair Labor Standards Act, 1961-1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  April 16, 1961-October 1971